CURRICULUM VITAE

SREENIVASU SENAPATHI

E-MAIL: SREENIVASU_23@REDIFFMAIL.COM

SREENIVASU.SENAPATHI@JOALI.COM

SKYPE ID: SREENIVASU 23

COMMUNICATION ADDRESS:

JOALI MALDIVES

C/o ALI BEY MALDIVES PVT. LTD.,

4TH FLOOR, H BEACH TOWER, BODUTHAKURUFAANU MAGU,

MALÉ 20066, REPUBLIC OF MALDIVES.

PHONE: +960 7784691 (MALDIVES) & +91 9000781841 (INDIA)



To obtain a challenging job in the field of **Information Technology / Systems** in a progressive organization that gives me a chance to update in accordance with the latest technologies, able to manage team or part of team that dynamically work towards the growth of the organization.

SUMMARY

Hospitality Information Technology Manager and Certified Professional in MICROSOFT, CISCO and ITIL® V3 with experience in Pre-Opening, IT Service Management, IT Infrastructure Support and Administration, IT Project Management, SLA Management, Vendor Management, Budgeting, Team Development and Management. Well versed in planning and deploying of hospitality applications within an organization with Multi-Property and complex business requirement.

EXPERIENCE

HOSPITALITY IT MANAGER : 12.0+ years (DEPARTMENT HEAD)

TOTAL HOSPITALITY IT : 14.0+ years OVERALL IT EXPERIENCE : 21.0+ years

PRE-OPENING EXPERIENCE

- JOALI Maldives Resort opened in September 2018 (presently working)
- Anantara Al Jabal Al Akhdar Resort in October 2016
- Desert Islands Resort and Spa by Anantara Renovation of IT infrastructure in June 2014 and upgrade of all systems from Single property to Multi-property setup in March 2013
- Anantara Sir Bani Yas Island Al Yamm Villa Resort in May 2013
- Anantara Sir Bani Yas Island Al Saleh Villa Resort in November 2013
- Rebranding to LUX* Maldives from Diva Maldives in January 2012

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- 1. Installation, Maintenance and upgradation of Windows 2008 and 2012 Servers.
- 2. Installing and configuring DNS, DHCP and IIS Servers in Windows 2008 and 2012
- 3. Installing and Configuring Windows 2008 and 2012 Active Directory Service
- 4. Troubleshooting Active Directory, related problems
- 5. Software Deployment in Windows 2008 and 2012 using Group Policies
- 6. Managing Backups and Restoration and data using VERITAS, NetVault, NTBACKUP and GHOST
- 7. Remote Administration through Terminal Services
- 8. Installing and Administering Network Print Server
- 9. Performing Volume Management on RAID 0, RAID1, RAID 5 and RAID 1+0

NETWORKING & WI-FI SKILLS

- Managing and Configuring of Network Switches, Access Points and Controllers Cisco, Avaya, Aruba and Huawei
- Managing of HSIA devices Useroam, Surfsonix, TigerTMS, Nomadix and ClearOS
- ✓ Planning and Implementation of Wi-Fi Network



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

> Presently working as Senior Information Technology Manager in JOALI Maldives Resort, Republic of Maldives (5* Ultra Luxury Resort) from Jan 2018 to till date.

Roles and Responsibilities

- ✓ Joined as a part of pre-opening team, actively involved in implementation all IT implementations.
- √ Implementing of IT policies accurately with support of management and other depts.
- ✓ Conducting of IT related trainings for IT Team and to other depts.
- √ Handling of IT Projects, SLA Management, Vendor Management, Budgeting OPEX and CAPEX
- ✓ Managing Datacenter operations.
- √ Implementation of Disaster Recovery Site and offline Data Backup management.
- ✓ Managing Huawei Network Managed Switches, VLAN config, 3CX Call Manager
- ✓ Managing Huawei Wireless Controller and Access Point
- ✓ Guest High Speed Internet Access using Useroam
- ✓ Installation and Upgrading of Operating System and Application Software
- ✓ Install security features on the network to deny the access
- ✓ Configuring and Maintenance of Local and Network printers for End-Users
- ✓ Installing Virus protection software on PC's and regularly updating with new patches
- ✓ Monitoring and performance tuning of the System OS and Application
- ✓ Monitoring the Network using TCP/IP utilities like PING, Ipconfig, and third party
- Network E-Sight Monitor Utility to test the connectivity and analyze the Network
- ✓ Backup of HDD and Partitions using Norton Ghost
- ✓ Configuring of Microsoft Outlook (MS O365 and Exchange)
- ✓ Backup and Restore of Mail Box in Outlook
- ✓ Maintenance of PC Hardware and Installing of required software
- ✓ Installation and Maintenance of Micros POS Terminals, KOT and Check printers
- ✓ Maintenance of Wi-Fi Network in entire Resort (Guest and Staff Areas)
- ✓ Managing CONTROL4 Room Automation System
- ✓ Knowledge on Interfaces

Opera PMS – POS,OXI,SALTO,Useroam,Control4,KNOWCROSS,3CX,RA,SunSystems & Salesforce FMC - POS and SunSystems

HR FUSION - SunSystems

- ✓ Pre-Opening Implementation, Managing and Configuring of
 - o Oracle Opera PMS Ver 5.6 Full Edition
 - o Oracle Simphony POS
 - o Oracle Material Control
 - o SunSystems 6 Financials
 - Query and Analysis for Opera PMS and SunSystems
 - o Fusion HR Payroll software
 - SALTO Door Lock System (RID Readers)
 - o Reservation Assistant Spa and Marine Center Reservation Management System
 - o KNOWCROSS Guest Service and Glitch Recovery Management System
- Worked as Information Technology Manager in Anantara Al Jabal Al Akhdar Resort, Nizwa, Sultanate of Oman (5* Luxury Resort) from Sep 2015 to Jan 2018.
- Worked as Multi-Property Information Technology Manager in Anantara Desert Islands Resort, Al Yamm Villas and Al Sahel Villas – Sir Bani Yas Island, Abu Dhabi, UAE (5* Luxury Resorts) from Oct 2012 to Sep 2015.
- Worked as Information Technology Manager in LUX* Maldives Resort (5* Luxury Resort) of LUX* Resorts and Hotels from Mar 2010 to Oct 2012.
- Worked as Head of Information Technology in Binary Investment Research Pvt. Ltd., Hyderabad, India from Jun 2008 to Jan 2010.
- Worked as Information Systems Administrator in TAJ Krishna, Hyderabad, India of TAJ Group of Hotels, Resorts and Palaces (5* Luxury and Member of the Leading Hotels of the World) from Nov 2006 to May 2008.

- Worked as Systems Executive in Katriya Hotel and Towers, Hyderabad, India from Mar 2006 to Nov 2006. (Formerly known as Fortune Katriya, Member of ITC's Hotel Group)
- > Worked as **Systems Administrator** in Govt. Polytechnic for Women, Kakinada, India from Jan 2003 to Dec 2005
- Worked as a faculty of C, C++ and Unix in Datapro Infoworld Ltd., Visakhapatnam, India May 2001 to Dec 2002

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Backup Tools

Operating Systems : Windows 2012 & 2016

> Windows 10,11, Linux, ClearOS : Norton Ghost, Veritas, Veeam

Mail Server : MS 0365, Exchange Server, MDaemon Office Automation Tools : MS-Office 2016 & 2019, Photoshop

Business Applications : Oracle (Opera PMS, Simphony POS and MC), IDS, Shawman

VPOS, Infogenesis, HR Fusion, Sapience HRMS, CHECK SCM, Vingcard, Onity, SALTO, FCS, KNOWCROSS, Booker,

Eat2Eat, Respak, Rategain RMS, TravelClick IBE.

TECHNICAL CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified Solutions Expert Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate Cisco Certified Network Associate ITIL® V3 in IT Service Management

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

- > Master in Business Administration in Corporate IT, Network & Telcom Management from Indian Institute of Business Management & Studies, Mumbai, INDIA
- Bachelor in Sciences in Mathematics, Physics and Computer Sciences from Andhra University, Visakhapatnam, AP, INDIA

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth : 11th February 1980

Nationality : India

Languages known : English, Hindi and Telugu

Marital Status : Single

Hobbies : Traveling, Experience New Cultures & Playing Cricket

DECLARATION

I hereby declared that the above information furnished by me are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

SREENIVASU SENAPATHI







